(Raj:)- You told her?
- l told everybody.
(Bernadette:)We believe there's someone out there
who'll love you for you.
(Howard:)We kind of agreed to disagree
on that one.
(Howard:)But we both think
you shouldn't marry this woman.
(Raj:)So while I'm waiting
for this mysterious perfect match...
(Raj:)...who may or may not exist,
I'm supposed to just be alone?
(Bernadette:)Not necessarily.
l think we found someone for you
to cuddle with.
(Raj:)Oh, my goodness.
(Raj:)Aren't you the cutest little Yorkie ever?
(Raj:)- You got him for me?
- Her.
(Howard:)We thought you two would hit it off.
l think we already have.
Thank you guys so much.
Let's go see if you fit in my man-purse.
(Bernadette:)Metrosexual, my ass.